ktbs.com 2018-01-16

# KTBS 3 Privacy Policy | Site | ktbs.com

    ARZ050-051-059>061-070>073-LAZ001>006-010>014-017>022-OKZ077-
    TXZ096-097-108>112-124>126-136>138-149>153-165>167-170030-
    /O.CON.KSHV.HZ.W.0004.180117T0200Z-180117T1600Z/
    Sevier-Howard-Little River-Hempstead-Nevada-Miller-Lafayette-
    Columbia-Union-Caddo-Bossier-Webster-Claiborne-Lincoln-De Soto-
    Red River-Bienville-Jackson-Ouachita-Sabine-Natchitoches-Winn-
    Grant-Caldwell-La Salle-McCurtain-Bowie-Franklin-Titus-Camp-
    Morris-Cass-Wood-Upshur-Marion-Smith-Gregg-Harrison-Cherokee-Rusk-
    Panola-Nacogdoches-Shelby-Angelina-San Augustine-
    Including the cities of De Queen, Nashville, Mineral Springs, 
    Dierks, Ashdown, Hope, Prescott, Texarkana, Stamps, Lewisville, 
    Bradley, Magnolia, El Dorado, Shreveport, Bossier City, Minden, 
    Springhill, Homer, Haynesville, Ruston, Farmerville, Bernice, 
    Mansfield, Stonewall, Logansport, Coushatta, Martin, Arcadia, 
    Ringgold, Gibsland, Jonesboro, Monroe, Many, Zwolle, 
    Pleasant Hill, Natchitoches, Winnfield, Colfax, Montgomery, 
    Dry Prong, Clarks, Grayson, Columbia, Jena, Midway, Olla, Idabel,
    Broken Bow, Clarksville, Bogata, Mount Vernon, Mount Pleasant, 
    Pittsburg, Daingerfield, Lone Star, Naples, Omaha, Atlanta, 
    Linden, Hughes Springs, Queen City, Mineola, Winnsboro, Quitman, 
    Hawkins, Gilmer, Big Sandy, Jefferson, Tyler, Longview, Marshall,
    Jacksonville, Rusk, Henderson, Carthage, Nacogdoches, Center, 
    Lufkin, San Augustine, Hemphill, and Pineland
    1016 AM CST Tue Jan 16 2018
    
    ...HARD FREEZE WARNING REMAINS IN EFFECT FROM 8 PM THIS EVENING
    TO 10 AM CST WEDNESDAY...
    
    * EVENT...Temperatures will plummet into the lower to middle teens
      resulting in hard freeze conditions. 
    
    * TIMING...Temperatures will remain well below freezing today and
      fall into the teens a few hours after sunset through mid-morning 
      tomorrow.
     
    * IMPACT...Take precautions to cover exposed pipes and bring pets
      indoors as well as protect sensitive outdoor plants.
    
    PRECAUTIONARY/PREPAREDNESS ACTIONS...
    
    A Hard Freeze Warning means sub-freezing temperatures are either
    imminent or occurring. These conditions will kill crops and other
    sensitive vegetation.
    
    &&
    
    $$

    ARZ050-051-059>061-070>073-LAZ001>006-010>014-017>022-OKZ077-
    TXZ096-097-108>112-124>126-136>138-149>153-165>167-171400-
    Sevier-Howard-Little River-Hempstead-Nevada-Miller-Lafayette-
    Columbia-Union-Caddo-Bossier-Webster-Claiborne-Lincoln-De Soto-
    Red River-Bienville-Jackson-Ouachita-Sabine-Natchitoches-Winn-
    Grant-Caldwell-La Salle-McCurtain-Bowie-Franklin-Titus-Camp-
    Morris-Cass-Wood-Upshur-Marion-Smith-Gregg-Harrison-Cherokee-Rusk-
    Panola-Nacogdoches-Shelby-Angelina-San Augustine-
    Including the cities of De Queen, Nashville, Mineral Springs, 
    Dierks, Ashdown, Hope, Prescott, Texarkana, Stamps, Lewisville, 
    Bradley, Magnolia, El Dorado, Shreveport, Bossier City, Minden, 
    Springhill, Homer, Haynesville, Ruston, Farmerville, Bernice, 
    Mansfield, Stonewall, Logansport, Coushatta, Martin, Arcadia, 
    Ringgold, Gibsland, Jonesboro, Monroe, Many, Zwolle, 
    Pleasant Hill, Natchitoches, Winnfield, Colfax, Montgomery, 
    Dry Prong, Clarks, Grayson, Columbia, Jena, Midway, Olla, Idabel, 
    Broken Bow, Clarksville, Bogata, Mount Vernon, Mount Pleasant, 
    Pittsburg, Daingerfield, Lone Star, Naples, Omaha, Atlanta, 
    Linden, Hughes Springs, Queen City, Mineola, Winnsboro, Quitman, 
    Hawkins, Gilmer, Big Sandy, Jefferson, Tyler, Longview, Marshall, 
    Jacksonville, Rusk, Henderson, Carthage, Nacogdoches, Center, 
    Lufkin, San Augustine, Hemphill, and Pineland
    1250 PM CST Tue Jan 16 2018
    
    ...Black Ice will remain a problem over all of the Ark-La-Tex
    This Afternoon through much of Wednesday...
    
    Widespread snowfall totals of one to three inches has fallen
    across much of the Ark La Tex this morning, with the snow expected
    to diminish across Deep East Texas and the southern sections of
    Northcentral Louisiana this afternoon. However, temperatures will
    remain below freezing this afternoon areawide, with the cloud
    cover expected to diminish along and south of the Interstate 20
    corridor by tonight. 
    
    The existing snowpack, clearing sky, and weakening winds will
    allow temperatures to quickly fall into teens and lower 20s this
    evening, and into the lower and middle teens areawide by 
    Wednesday morning. As a result, any melting snow on the roadways, 
    bridges, and overpasses this afternoon will quickly refreeze into
    black ice this evening, making travel very treacherous. 
    Temperatures will only warm slowly Wednesday, but will likely 
    remain below freezing until early to mid afternoon, if at all. 
    Thus, black ice on area roadways will remain a problem through 
    much of Wednesday, with this threat again increasing Wednesday 
    night as temperatures fall into the teens once again. 
    
    Travel is strongly discouraged across the region this afternoon
    through Wednesday. If you must travel this afternoon or tonight,
    please drive slowly, allow plenty of time to reach your
    destination, and allow extra space between you and the other 
    drivers around you. Be sure you pack a winter weather survival 
    kit, by including food, water, extra blankets, a flashlight, and 
    provide a means to charge your cell phone or other electronic 
    devices in case you are stranded. Be sure you have a full tank of 
    gas before leaving as well. 
    
    $$

    ARZ050-051-059>061-070>073-LAZ001>004-006-OKZ077-TXZ096-097-
    108>112-124>126-136>138-149>151-170200-
    /O.CON.KSHV.WC.Y.0003.180117T0200Z-180117T1600Z/
    Sevier-Howard-Little River-Hempstead-Nevada-Miller-Lafayette-
    Columbia-Union-Caddo-Bossier-Webster-Claiborne-McCurtain-
    Red River-Bowie-Franklin-Titus-Camp-Morris-Cass-Wood-Upshur-
    Marion-Smith-Gregg-Harrison-Cherokee-Rusk-Panola-
    Including the cities of De Queen, Nashville, Mineral Springs, 
    Dierks, Ashdown, Hope, Prescott, Texarkana, Stamps, Lewisville, 
    Bradley, Magnolia, El Dorado, Shreveport, Bossier City, Minden, 
    Springhill, Homer, Haynesville, Farmerville, Bernice, Idabel, 
    Broken Bow, Clarksville, Bogata, Mount Vernon, Mount Pleasant, 
    Pittsburg, Daingerfield, Lone Star, Naples, Omaha, Atlanta, 
    Linden, Hughes Springs, Queen City, Mineola, Winnsboro, Quitman, 
    Hawkins, Gilmer, Big Sandy, Jefferson, Tyler, Longview, Marshall,
    Jacksonville, Rusk, Henderson, and Carthage
    1242 PM CST Tue Jan 16 2018
    
    ...WIND CHILL ADVISORY REMAINS IN EFFECT FROM 8 PM THIS EVENING
    TO 10 AM CST WEDNESDAY...
    ...WINTER STORM WARNING HAS EXPIRED...
    
    * WHAT...Dangerously cold wind chills will develop tonight after
      sunset with readings falling into the single digits areawide. 
    
    * WHERE...Portions of south central Arkansas, southwest Arkansas,
      northwest Louisiana and northeast Texas.
    
    * WHEN...8 PM tonight through 10 AM Wednesday.
    
    * ADDITIONAL DETAILS...The cold wind chills will cause frostbite 
      in as little as 30 minutes to any exposed skin.
    
    PRECAUTIONARY/PREPAREDNESS ACTIONS...
    
    A Wind Chill Advisory means that cold air and the wind will
    combine to create low wind chills. Frost bite and hypothermia can
    occur if precautions are not taken. Make sure you wear a hat and
    gloves.
    
    &&
    
    $$

#### Closings

June 4, 2007

### What this Privacy Policy Covers

### This Privacy Policy covers:

KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc.'s treatment of personally identifiable information that KTBS.com collects when you are on the KTBS.com site, and when you use KTBS.com's services. This policy also covers KTBS.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that KTBS.com's business partners share with KTBS.com or that KTBS.com may collect on a partner's site. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. does not own or control, or to people that KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. does not employ or manage.

### Information Collection and Use

KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. collects personally identifiable information when you register for a KTBS.com account, when you use certain KTBS.com products or services, when you visit KTBS.com pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. KTBS.com may also receive personally identifying information from our business partners. Prior to providing KTBS.com with information, you will be offered a link that allows you to review this privacy policy and you will be provided with an opportunity to opt-out of certain uses of your personal information when applicable.

When you register with KTBS.com, we ask for your name, email address, physical address, zip code, phone and fax numbers, and comments. If you are commenting on a story, you will be required to provide your Facebook username and password if you are not already logged as a Facebook user. Once you register with KTBS.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

KTBS.com uses information for two general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about new products.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

  * We have your consent to share the information; We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; We require opt-in consent to share your personally identifiable information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or We find that your actions on our website violate the KTBS.com [Terms of Service](https://www.ktbs.com/site/terms.html) or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services

### Cookies

When you visit KTBS.com, we send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some KTBS.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to KTBS.com's cookies.

To request changes to or deletion of your KTBS.com account, and to read about what information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted email us at [bpollitt@ktbs.com](mailto:bpollitt@ktbs.com).

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
